A Finding Aid to the Holly Solomon Gallery Records, circa 1948-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.hollsolg
Archives of American Art
Holly Solomon Gallery records
circa 1948-2003
AAA.hollsolg
Archives of American Art
196.1 Linear feet
The records of Holly Solomon Gallery, a New York City gallery specializing in contemporary American art, measure 196.1 linear feet and date from circa 1948-2003. The gallery's activities are documented through dealer files, subject files, artists' files, inventories, sales and loan records, administrative and financial records, printed materials, photographic materials of artwork and exhibitions, sound, video, and film recordings, and scattered electronic records. Also found are records of the alternative space, 98 Greene Street Loft, as well as Holly Solomon's personal papers.
Holly Solomon Gallery
Provenance
The collection was donated in 2010 by Thomas and John Solomon, Holly Solomon's sons.
Restrictions on Access
This collection is access restricted. Use requires written permission. Financial and Legal Records (Series 8) are closed to researchers until they can be processed to a more detailed level.
Historical Note
The Holly Solomon Gallery was established in 1975 by Holly Solomon and her husband, Horace Solomon, at 392 West Broadway in New York City's SoHo area. The gallery focused on contemporary art.
The gallery represented artists such as William Wegman, Nam June Paik, Laurie Anderson, and Robert Kushner. In 1983, the gallery moved uptown to 724 Fifth Ave at 57th, but then moved again in the early 1990s back downtown to SoHo at 172 Mercer Street. After the gallery closed Holly Solomon continued to deal art from the Chelsea Hotel until her death in 2002.
Holly Solomon was born Hollis Dworken in Bridgeport, Connecticut in 1934. She started college at Vassar College, and later transferred to Sarah Lawrence College where she graduated in 1955. In 1953 she married Horace Solomon. Holly Solomon was an aspiring stage actress and was enrolled at Lee Strasberg's Actor's Studio shortly after moving to Manhattan. Although she was not a successful actress she and her husband began collecting art and were fans of the Pop Art movement. In 1969 the couple opened an alternative work and performance space for artists named 98 Greene Street Loft. The space provided a venue for poets, actors, and artists to work and perform. Solomon wrote and produced a five part documentary from performances at 98 Greene Street, and in 1972 it was shown at the Edinburgh International Film Festival. 98 Greene Street Loft closed in 1973. Holly Solomon was also a proponent of the Pattern and Decoration, or "P and D", art movement of the late 1970s and early 1980s. Many of the artists featured in her gallery were involved in the P and D movement including Robert Kushner, Kim MacConnel, Ned Smyth, and Brad Davis.
Scope and Content Note
The records of Holly Solomon Gallery, a New York City gallery specializing in contemporary American art, measure 196.1 linear feet and date from circa 1948-2003. The gallery's activities are documented through alphabetical files, dealer files, subject files, artists' files, inventories, sales and loan records, administrative and financial records, printed materials, photographic materials of artwork and exhibitions, sound, video, and film recordings, and scattered electronic records. Also found are records of the alternative space, 98 Greene Street Loft, as well as Holly Solomon's personal papers.
Alphabetical files span from 1991-2000 and contain correspondence with clients, galleries, and museums, as well as related documentation regarding loans, inquiries, sales, exhibitions, and travel plans. These general files were maintained separately from the gallery's subject and artists' files but may overlap in subject matter.
The dealer files contain gallery correspondence to and from art dealers regarding inquiries on works and artists. These files are sparse and particular to the early 1980s. Subject files are mainly comprised of correspondence but also include printed materials, slides, and other related documents. Subjects include dealers, organizations, museums, clients, art fairs, travel, and projects that the gallery or Holly Solomon worked with.
Artists' files consist of correspondence, printed material, slides, photographs, and scattered inventory records, regarding the sale of artwork, as well as shipping records and insurance claims. Also included is correspondence between the gallery and the artist. There is substantial documentation on artists Kim MacConnel, Nam June Paik, Izhar Patkin, William Wegman, and Joe Zucker. Inventory records include inventory lists created by Holly Solomon Gallery as well as an art inventory card file. Inventory cards note the title, date, and size of the work as well as the dates and movements of the work, and may include a photograph.
Administrative records contain general office materials such as phone messages books, staff notebooks, exhibition guest books, and business diaries, exhibition documentation, notes, and mail from prospective artists. Records primarily cover the 1980s and 1990s. In addition to business diaries, Holly Solomon also created "Dear Diary" binders which contain a collection of contact information and notes on clients and events. Some of these diaries were maintained for specific events.
Sales and loan records consist of in and out sheets, consignments, and sales invoices. Also in this series are sales and loan logs and files that track the same information but from different access points, including sales by artist. Financial records document the financial activities of the galleries, apart from sales, and include shipping records, tax and insurance information, and accounting statements and reports. Also found in this series are bills, receipts, and several ledgers. Legal records primarily document issues with the landlord of the gallery space.
Printed material consists of artist clippings, gallery exhibition catalogs, press releases, posters, and miscellaneous books, magazines, and clippings regarding the gallery. Included are clippings pertaining to the Pattern and Design art movement. Photographic material includes photographs and slides documenting artists' work and gallery exhibitions. Sound, video, and film recordings include artworks created by gallery artists, performances recorded live at the gallery, and the publicity Holly Solomon, the gallery and its artists received. The work of video artist Nam June Paik is highly represented through some of his video artworks, as well as television interviews with him. Prominent artists William Wegman and Laurie Anderson are also represented through original artworks and publicity. Publicity videos include Holly Solomon herself, being interviewed for television and documentaries.
The records of 98 Greene Street Loft include a large quantity of sound, video, and film recordings of poetry readings, live music, art, and theatrical performances that took place from 1971-1973, as well as scattered paper records such as play scripts, photographs, a guest book from 1971, printed material, and posters.
Holly Solomon's personal papers consist of biographical documents, correspondence, memorabilia, printed material, motion picture film, and photographs collected by Holly Solomon throughout her life. Included are school records, letters, notes and cards from friends and artists she represented at her gallery, photographs, invitations, event fliers, and other mementos. Printed material, mostly magazines and newspapers document her accomplishments.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 14 series:
Series 1: Alphabetical Files, 1991-2001 (Boxes 1-9; 8.5 linear feet)
Series 2: Dealer Files, 1980-1990 (Box 9-10; 1.5 linear feet)
Series 3: Subject Files, circa 1975-2002 (Boxes 11-25; 15.0 linear feet)
Series 4: Artists' Files, circa 1975-2002 (Boxes 26-47; 22.0 linear feet)
Series 5: Inventory Records, 1975-2001 (Boxes 48-66, 157-162; 25.0 linear feet)
Series 6: Administrative Records, circa 1980-2003 (Boxes 67-81, OV 202; 15.1 linear feet)
Series 7: Sales and Loan Records, circa 1975-2001 (Boxes 82-87; 6.0 linear feet)
Series 8: Financial and Legal Records, circa 1969-2001 (Boxes 88-114, 191, 192; 27.7 linear feet)
Series 9: Printed Material, circa 1968-2002 (Boxes 115-135, 193-194, OV 203-222, RD 223; 23.5 linear feet)
Series 10: Photographic Material, circa 1969-2000 (Boxes 136-156, 194-196, 201, OV 224; 22.2 linear feet)
Series 11: 98 Greene Street Loft, circa 1969-1973 (Boxes 166-169, 197-200, OV 225-227; 5.5 linear feet)
Series 12: Holly Solomon Personal Papers, circa 1948-2002 (Boxes 170-182, 194; 13.1 linear feet)
Series 13: Sound, Video, and Film Recordings, circa 1966-2001 (Boxes 183-190; 7.6 linear feet)
Series 14: Electronic Records, (Box 190; 0.4 linear feet)
The collection has been minimally arranged into series based on the found arrangement upon receipt, assumed to be the original arrangement of the gallery. Folders have been arranged within series and general folder contents verified, but in most cases, item level arrangement has not been completed.
98 Green St. Loft; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; MacConnel, Kim; Paik, Nam June, 1932-; Patkin, Izhar; Solomon, Holly; Wegman, William; Zucker, Joe, 1941-; Art galleries, Commercial--New York (State)--New York; Daybooks; Diaries; Interviews; Motion pictures (visual works); Notebooks; Performance art; Photographs; Sound recordings; Video art; Video recordings; Visitors' books
- Alphabetical Files, 1991-2001; Series 1; (Boxes 1-9; 8.5 linear feet)
  Scope and Contents note
  The alphabetical files span from 1991-2000 and contain miscellaneous incoming and outgoing gallery correspondence with clients, galleries, and museums regarding loans, inquiries, sales, exhibitions, and travel plans. Some of the correspondence includes printed materials, slides, and other related documents. These files were maintained separately from the gallery's subject and artists' files for any correspondence that did not have enough bulk to warrant its own file. There may also be some overlap with Series 3: Subject Files and Series 4: Artists' Files for items that were accidentally filed in these general files instead of into the proper subject or artist file. Additional correspondence can also be found within the dealer files, administrative records, and financial and legal records.
  Arrangement note
  Items are filed alphabetically by company name or last name. Within each letter of the alphabet, items were also filed by year.
  - A, 1991-2000; (12 folders) (Box 1)
  - B, 1991-1997; (10 folders) (Box 1)
  - B, 1998-2000; (3 folders) (Box 2)
  - C, 1991-2000; (11 folders) (Box 2)
  - D, 1991-1996; (5 folders) (Box 2)
  - D, 1997-2000; (4 folders) (Box 3)
  - E, 1991-2000; (4 folders) (Box 3)
  - F, 1991-2001; (9 folders) (Box 3)
  - G, 1991-1993; (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - G, 1992-2000; (5 folders) (Box 4)
  - H, 1991-2000; (6 folders) (Box 4)
  - I, 1991-2000; (4 folders) (Box 4)
  - J, 1991-2000; (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - K, 1991-2000; (7 folders) (Box 5)
  - L, 1991-2000; (6 folders) (Box 5)
  - M, 1991-1992; (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - M, 1992-2000; (7 folders) (Box 6)
  - N, 1991-2000; (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - O, 1991-2000; (4 folders) (Box 6)
  - P 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - P 1991-2000, (5 folders) (Box 7)
  - Q, 1992-1993, 1997, 2000; (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - R, 1991-2000; (5 folders) (Box 7)
  - S, 1991-1993; (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - S, 1992-2000; (9 folders) (Box 8)
  - T, 1991-2000; (7 folders) (Box 8)
  - U, 1991-2000; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - V, 1991-2000; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - W, 1991-2000; (5 folders) (Box 9)
  - X, Y, and Z, 1991-1995; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Y, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
  - Z, 1996-2000 (Box 9)
- Dealer Files, 1980-1990; Series 2; (Box 9-10; 1.5 linear feet)
  The dealer files contain gallery correspondence to and from art dealers regarding inquiries on works and artists. These files are sparse and particular to the early 1980s. For more dealer files researchers should review Series 3: Subject Files.
  Files are maintained in the original gallery arrangement, alphabetically by location of dealer (i.e., state, country, or region). Folder titles have been transcribed from the existing folder labels.
  - Dealers - California (Box 9)
    - Atlantic Richfield, 1981-1984 (Box 9)
    - Joni Gordon/Newspace, 1981-1986 (Box 9)
    - Harcourts Contemporary, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
    - Judy Kay/San Francisco, 1982-1986 (Box 9)
    - Rubicon Gallery, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
    - Santa Barbara Arts Forum, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Joan Simon/Functional Art Show, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Bruce Velick Gallery, 1983-1985 (Box 9)
    - California- Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 9)
    - World Print Council/Leslie Luebbers, 1983-1986 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Colorado (Box 9)
    - Robischon Gallery, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Janie Beggs Fine Arts, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Unicorn Gallery, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Connecticut (Box 9)
    - Parson Webb Gallery, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Washington, DC (Box 9)
    - Brody's Gallery, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Jean Efron, 1982-1986 (Box 9)
    - McIntosh/Drysdale Gallery, 1981-1986 (Box 9)
    - Washington, DC Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Florida (Box 9)
    - Fay Gold Gallery, 1981-1986 (Box 9)
    - Center for the Contemporary Arts, 1984-1986 (Box 9)
    - Carol Getz, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Norton Art Gallery, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Tampa Art Museum, 1983 (Box 9)
    - University of West Florida Gallery, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Georgia (Box 9)
    - Coca-Cola, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Hawaii (Box 9)
    - Marvin Heifferman/Liberty House, undated (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Illinois (Box 9)
    - Barbara Balkin, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Dart Gallery, 1981-1983 (Box 9)
    - Sondra Eisenberg, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Hokin Gallery, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Landfall Press, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
    - Lillstreet Gallery, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Larson Associates Inc., 1986 (Box 9)
    - Chicago Musuem of Contemporary Art, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Iowa (Box 9)
    - Perciva Galleries, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Kansas/Missouri (Box 9)
    - Brentwood Gallery, 1984 (Box 9)
    - University of Missouri, Kansas City, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Louisiana (Box 9)
    - Elmhurst Park Gallery, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - University of South Louisiana, 1981 (Box 9)
    - New Orleans, Louisiana Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Maryland (Box 9)
    - G.H. Dalsheimer Gallery, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Baltimore Musuem of Art, 1981-1983 (Box 9)
    - Sylvia Cordish Fine Arts, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Dealers - Massachusetts (Box 10)
    - Aptekar Arts Management, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Cutler Stavaridis Gallery, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Krakow Gallery/Cell Friedman, undated (Box 10)
    - Portia Harcus Gallery, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Magnuson Lee Gallery, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Thomas Segal Gallery, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Michigan (Box 10)
    - Cantor Lemberg Gallery, 1981-1986 (Box 10)
    - Lee Hoffman Gallery, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Minnesota (Box 10)
    - Lynne Sowder and Associates, 1982-1986 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - New Jersey (Box 10)
    - Art of Our Time, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - Prudential Ins. Co., 1980-1981 (Box 10)
    - Rutgers Print Archives, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - New Jersey Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - New Mexico, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - New York (Box 10)
    - A.I.P.A.D., 1984 (Box 10)
    - Artists Space, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Bellette Hofmann, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Castelli Goodman Solomon Gallery, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
    - Elizabeth Galasso Fine Arts Leasing, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Franklin Furnace, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Carol Goldberg, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Hudson General Corp., 1981 (Box 10)
    - Corporate Art Directions/Betty Levin, 1982 (Box 10)
    - New Musuem, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Paperworks Gallery, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Paris Review, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Salomon Brothers/Peggy Kutsen, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Stacker, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Thorpe Intermedia Gallery, 1981 (Box 10)
    - 28 St. Gallery/Andrew Veljkovic, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
    - Diane Villani, 1982-1986 (Box 10)
    - Ward Gallery, Sibley's, 1983 (Box 10)
    - New York Sales, 1986 (Box 10)
  - New York Corporate (Box 10)
    - Chase Bank/Jack Boulton, 1982-1985 (Box 10)
    - Fine Arts Planning Group/Nancy Rosen, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Reader's Digest, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Randy Rosen GE, 1983 (Box 10)
  - New York Museums (Box 10)
    - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Albright-Knox, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Dog Museum of America, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Viart, 1983-1986 (Box 10)
    - Wilson Arts Center/Michael Lasser, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Musuem of Modern Art, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
    - Jamaica Arts Center/William Miller, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Museum Tower/Sally Ludlow, 1983-1986 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - North Carolina (Box 10)
    - Ackland Art Musuem/Innis Shoemaker, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Ohio (Box 10)
    - Carl Solway Gallery, 1981-1986 (Box 10)
    - The New Gallery, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Columbus Art Museum, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Ruth Meyer/OFA Traveling Show, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Oklahoma, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Pennsylvania (Box 10)
    - Diane Dunning Associates, 1984-1985 (Box 10)
    - Marcus Gordon Associates, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - The Fabric Workshop, 1980-1983 (Box 10)
    - CIGNA Corporation, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Philadelphia Art Museum, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Rhode Island (Box 10)
    - RISD Museum, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Seabreeze Gallery, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Texas (Box 10)
    - Delahunty Gallery, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
    - Kaufman Galleries, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Ben Holland/Carancahua Gallery, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Mattingly-Baker Gallery, 1981-1988 (Box 10)
    - Betty Moody Gallery, 1982-1983 (Box 10)
    - Texas Gallery, 1983-1986 (Box 10)
    - Frito Lay Inc, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Virginia (Box 10)
    - Chrystler Museum, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Washington (Box 10)
    - Foster/White Gallery, 1982-1986 (Box 10)
    - Linda Farris Gallery, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - West Virginia (Box 10)
    - Raymond Hage, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Wisconsin (Box 10)
    - Michael Lord Gallery, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Milwaukee Art Museum, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Madison Arts Center, 1982-1986 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Europe (Box 10)
    - Galerie Barbara Farber/American Graffiti, 1982-1984 (Box 10)
    - ArtCurial, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - Konrad Fischer, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Grita Insam "Franen 84", 1984 (Box 10)
    - Davis Grob/12 Duke Street Gallery, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Kestner-Gesellschaft, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Paris Biennale/Georges Boudaillie, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Twigg-Smith, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Dr. Eswald Rathke, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Riekje Swart/Galerie Swart, 1983-1986 (Box 10)
    - Wm Verstraeten, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Far East (Box 10)
    - Fugi Gallery, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Dealers - Latin America (Box 10)
    - Museo Tamayo, 1983 (Box 10)
- Subject Files, circa 1975-2002; Series 3; (Boxes 11-25; 15.0 linear feet)
  The subject files are mainly comprised of correspondence but also include printed materials, slides, and other related documents. The files span the life of the gallery from 1975 to 2002. Subjects include dealers, organizations, museums, clients, art fairs, travel, and projects that the gallery or Holly Solomon worked with. Researchers should note that some artists' information is contained within this series, and these files should be consulted along with files in Series 4: Artists' Files. There is significant coverage on Holly Solomon's work with the Art Dealer's Association of America, as well as the gallery's participation in events like FIAC (International Contemporary Art Fair), and the gallery's relationship with Museum of Modern Art (MOMA.)
  Folders are arranged in alphabetical order by subject. Folder titles in this listing have been transcribed from the existing folder labels. For folders missing labels, titles were given based on the material in the file. Folder titles assigned by the archivist are indicated by brackets.
  - Abrams (W.W.), 1983-1992 (Box 11)
  - Advertising, 1975-1981 (Box 11)
  - Advertising Agency, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1983-1996 (Box 11)
  - Albuquerque, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, 1985-1998 (Box 11)
  - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1983-1991 (Box 11)
  - American Craft Museum, 1987-1991 (Box 11)
  - American Express, 1985-1996 (Box 11)
  - The American Assembly "Arts", 1997 (Box 11)
  - Ammann Fine Art, 1983-1994 (Box 11)
  - ARC-Musee d'Art Moderne-Paris, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Aronson (Mark Twain Blancshares), 1985-1998 (Box 11)
  - Art Dealer's Association of America [ADAA], 1983-2001; (10 folders) (Box 11)
  - Art Fair, New York, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
  - [Art Fairs], 1997 (Box 12)
  - Artforum, 1985-1997 (Box 12)
  - ArtNet, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
  - Art Museum Association, 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Art Table, 1983-2000 (Box 12)
  - Art in America, 1991-1996 (Box 12)
  - Aspen Art Museum, 1986-1990 (Box 12)
  - Aspen Center for the Visual Arts, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Bank of New York, 1980-1984 (Box 12)
  - Notebook, Bologna/Basel, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Basel Art 8, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Basel (Kunsthalle), 1986-1998; (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Basel, 1991-1996 (Box 12)
  - Basel, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Galerie Beauborg, 1989-1991 (Box 12)
  - Beauborg (Centre Pompidou), 1983-1993 (Box 12)
  - Galerie Jurgen Becker, 1991-1994 (Box 12)
  - Berini, circa 1990s (Box 12)
  - Berlin Art Fair, 1996-1997; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - Berlin Art Fair '96, 1996 (Box 13)
  - George Bellows, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Bob Benamou, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Biennial, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Blancpain/Stepczynski, 1983-1992; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Blanpain, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Bomb Magazine, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
  - Bologna, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Marilena Bonomo, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Bourcharo - Copyright Lawyer, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1985-1994 (Box 13)
  - Bugdahn, 1994-1996 (Box 13)
  - Business Trips, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Cappellini, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Cape Bordeaux, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Carnegie Museum, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Laura Carpenter, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Carre, 1983-1990 (Box 13)
  - Castello di Rivara, 1991 (Box 13)
  - Chagall, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Charleston Trust, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1984-1992 (Box 13)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1985-1994 (Box 13)
  - Chicago 89/90, 1989-1992; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Chicago Art Fair, 1986-1998 (Box 13)
  - Chicago Art Expo-Insurance, 1984-1994 (Box 14)
  - Christies (All), 1985-1998; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Cirker City Storage Warehouse, 1983-1992; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Clairet, 1988-1992; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - C of O, 1988 (Box 14)
  - Cora Cohen, 1984-1989 (Box 14)
  - Contests, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Conservation, 1978-1985 (Box 14)
  - James Corcoran, 1983-1992 (Box 14)
  - Corcoran Museum, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
  - Crown Point Press, 1985-1990 (Box 14)
  - [D Miscellaneous], 1984-1994 (Box 14)
  - Damasquire Gallery, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Dannheisser Foundation, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
  - Danziger, 1979-1988 (Box 14)
  - Delaware Art Museum, 1986-1988 (Box 14)
  - Denmark, Kunsthallen Brandts, 1991-1994 (Box 14)
  - Detroit Institute of Fine Arts, 1985-1996 (Box 14)
  - DGA - Alarm, 1999-2001 (Box 14)
  - Dietman, 1993, 1997 (Box 14)
  - Galerie Di Meo, 1989-1996 (Box 14)
  - Max Dolgicer, 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - Michel Durand-Dessert, 1989-1992 (Box 14)
  - Durstmuller, circa 1990s (Box 14)
  - Raoul Dufy-Correspondence, circa 1980s (Box 14)
  - Dworken, Don, 1984-1989 (Box 14)
  - Sondra Ward Eisenberg, 1985, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Andre Emmerich Gallery, 1985-1996 (Box 14)
  - Epstein, 1975 (Box 14)
  - El Maleh, Victor, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Europe, June 1982 (Box 14)
  - Europe, June 1984 (Box 14)